Sheikh Al-Banna had a particular slot on Cairo radio where he read the Quran.
All the others were changed. The times, the dates changed but not sheikh Al-Banna. He always recited
Quran at six o'clock in the morning every Tuesday on Cairo radio for as long as I
lived in Egypt and after that. So, here I have a time, six o'clock in the morning, and the day
Tuesday. OK. So, I went to Mecca for, for the pilgrimage. My parents were with me and we
prayed the morning, the Fajr at the Kaaba and then we came back to our room.
and I was preparing... that was Tuesday... I was preparing to hear my favorite reciter on Cairo radio.
So, I got my little radio and I sat in bed. My father, my mother sat in the same room in
their beds and I turned the radio to Cairo and sure enough, here comes sheikh Al-Banna and I can tell you
the reason I know I was fully awake is I never never never never fall asleep when sheikh Al-Banna is reading
Quran. And when I... when I went for Hajj from here, I took with me a hundred cassette tapes and I gave them to my
brother Atef and I told him, specifically, I want you to record anything that Al-Banna comes
whenever it comes on the radio or the TV or anything, record it. This hundred tapes. I want them full
of recitations of sheikh Al-Banna. OK. So, in Mecca now... back to Mecca, Tuesday, I'm sitting in my bed
turning the radio to Cairo radio. There comes sheikh Al-Banna and he recites SURAT Al-Rahman
بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمٰنِ الرَّحِيْمِ
(55:1) ٱلرَّحْمَـٰنُ
(55:2) عَلَّمَ ٱلْقُرْءَانَ
(55:3) خَلَقَ ٱلْإِنسَـٰنَ
and I am in ecstasy.
and then, I didn't hear Al-Banna anymore. I was taken to some place in the universe
and I... and I know I was fully awake but here I am somewhere and I saw these... at the time
nothing was explained to me. It is none of your business now but you are here
for some reason. And I was... I saw... all I was told was that these are all the Prophets: Jesus, Moses
Muhammad, David, Solomon, Jonah, Lot, Noah, all of them. I was told this is all of them and they
appeared like those oval pictures that many of us have, except these are alive people that people...
God showed them to me the way they looked in this world because I probably would have freaked out
if God showed them to me in any other way and they have their different dresses, different
turbans and different robes but the person was ovally was down from, like, the head to
the knees. And one by one... they came in one by one and they looked straight in my face and they shake their
heads approvingly. Something like this, approvingly. And then the person would go like that.
And another one will come this way and so on. They kept going like this and I didn't know which is which.
Only Abraham was identified to me. When Abraham came, I was told this is Abraham.
And he's the only one identified to me and I didn't know what this was all about. Then, this ended. And when I
came back, I looked at my father and I said guess what! I just... I just met all the prophets and Abraham
was identified to me and he looks like us. Because it struck me, the resemblance, I remember what
they look like. Well, I can't tell which is which. So, I told him Abraham looks like
us, the Khalifas, you know what I mean. Look at me. Look at my brother. Look at my sister. There's a particular look and
Abraham looked like that. So, but the first thing that my father said was what did Muhammad look like?
I said sorry dad. I don't know which one was he but when I see him I recognize him again and we'll tell him what the name is .
OK. So, I just... I enjoyed it very much and I told my... my parents and I told my friends. I think
I mentioned it, maybe, to Soad in passing. It was not important to me. It was just... cause like I said it
was done like it is none of your business. This is just something to be done. So, to make a long story
short, four months ago, this was all explained to me and this is why I've been telling you that
ALLAH SUBHANAHU WA TA'ALA has been Merciful and Graceful towards us and that in SURA 3, verse 81, it was explained to me
that this is in fulfillment of this verse. That in retrospect what happened was that God took the
person, the Rashad Khalifa, to that place somewhere in the universe and the prophets, they were told this is
the person who is to confirm all your messages and to confirm all of you. Do you approve? Do you
fulfill your pledge to Me that We took before creation? And every one of them was now
explained. Now, that it is explained, I know what happened. So, they come in and they look in my
face and they say yes, we do. Yes, we we agree. We support him. We believe. And this is the
explanation that came to me. So, specifically, verse 81 of SURA 3 is what makes me dwell on that
verse because we are told and God told us now. I believe there are many many many messengers
because of what the Quran says. You know that if I tell you anything that is not Quranic,
you tell me get out of here. And I'll be the first to denounce that. But God says, in SURA 16
يُنَزِّلُ ٱلْمَلَـٰٓئِكَةَ بِٱلرُّوحِ مِنْ أَمْرِهِۦ عَلَىٰ مَن يَشَآءُ مِنْ عِبَادِهِۦٓ أَنْ (16:2) أَنذِرُوٓا۟ أَنَّهُۥ لَآ إِلَـٰهَ إِلَّآ أَنَا۠ فَٱتَّقُونِ
Excuse me, I mixed this with SURA 4.
يُنَزِّلُ ٱلْمَلَـٰٓئِكَةَ
He sends down the angels
بِٱلرُّوحِ
with inspiration or revelation or information.
This is what a RUH is
يُنَزِّلُ ٱلْمَلَـٰٓئِكَةَ بِٱلرُّوحِ مِنْ أَمْرِهِۦ
in accordance with His commands
عَلَىٰ مَن يَشَآءُ مِنْ عِبَادِهِۦٓ
upon whomever He wills from among his servants. Servants. Plural.
أَنْ أَنذِرُوٓا۟
that you shall preach
أَنَّهُۥ لَآ إِلَـٰهَ إِلَّآ أَنَا۠
that there is no god...
لا اله الا الله
that there is...
أَنَّهُۥ لَآ إِلَـٰهَ إِلَّآ أَنَا۠
فاعبدون
or
فَٱتَّقُونِ
I forget now
The other verses in SURA 40
where He says, in the present tense, now this is in the present tense
and the verse in SURA 40 I have to try to remember it now.
It's in the beginning of SURA 40. Edip will get it. But there's another verse in another SURA that says
ٱللَّهُ يَصْطَفِى
You know this one very well.
(22:75) ٱللَّهُ يَصْطَفِى مِنَ ٱلْمَلَـٰٓئِكَةِ رُسُلًا وَمِنَ ٱلنَّاسِ
God chooses from among the angels and from the people رُسُلًا, messengers.
There are many kinds of messengers. And I've got news for you. You are
messengers. You deliver the message: LA ILLAHA ILLA ALLAH.
Every one of you when you meet someone and you tell them to worship God alone, you are
messengers. Many many messengers. And you know you are. You are delivering God's message but
this particular instant makes me just one of you, but makes me one who is named or just given
a special, not special, specific, a specific mission. But we are all doing this and God
says this in SURA number two. He said
(22:78) لِيَكُونَ ٱلرَّسُولُ شَهِيدًا عَلَيْكُمْ
So, the messenger will be a witness among you
(22:78) وَتَكُونُوا۟ شُهَدَآءَ عَلَى ٱلنَّاسِ
and you be witnesses among the people.
This is in the Quran. Every one of you serve as witnesses, messengers. And the same word equally
used in that verse.
(22:78) لِيَكُونَ ٱلرَّسُولُ شَهِيدًا عَلَيْكُمْ وَتَكُونُوا۟ شُهَدَآءَ عَلَى ٱلنَّاسِ
The messenger will serve as a witness among you and you serve as witnesses among the people. So, you
have a fantastic responsibility and I know you're doing it pleasantly and tirelessly.
The verse... the verse in SURA 40...Oh, this is in Mu'minûn. What is this?
Oh, yes.
ٱللَّهُ يَصْطَفِى
Yeah, I said that one.
This is in SURA 23
(22:75) ٱللَّهُ يَصْطَفِى مِنَ ٱلْمَلَـٰٓئِكَةِ رُسُلًا
This is in the present tense.
Some people say that the inspiration or revelation ended by Muhammad. It's not true because this is in
the present tense. This is the final message. Everything is here. And we do not do anything
that is not here. But there is so much information here, it will keep coming until the end of the
world. Information that our parents did not know. Information that we do not know, and information
that our grandchildren only are destined to know. It's all in here. Nothing new, but it is all
in here including the end of the world and things that outrage the disbelievers.
The verse in SURA 40 that also explains this... this turned out to be a very important discussion here.
Ismail: Of course! What are you talking about?!
So, it may take time, but I'd like to read it correctly. It's right here.
It's very possible that I misplaced the verse, but I can't find it in SURA 40. But the
evidence is abundant that God uses, as you know, the Quran is mostly in the past tense
because God is telling us things in our future that are not future to God. They're
past as far as God is concerned. So, most of the Quran is in the past tense but when
it comes to selecting messengers, plural, in the Quran, it is in the present tense.
So, especially, in your case being the first... the first group, the pioneers of restoring
all God's messages of the past, you have a special responsibility. There are many many messengers and
this also confirms or is confirmed by the verse in Quran that says there is not a village that does not
have a messenger. So, this tells us how many messengers there are. But this incident that Carlos
asking about, just gives me a specific responsibility and makes us know precisely
what the deal is. Cause if you... if we are, if we are believers in the Quran,
we read in SURA 3, verse 81 that after all the prophets have come, after all the
prophets have come including Muhammad as you see in later on, God set a trap on the disbelievers.
After all the prophets have come, a messenger will come to confirm them. This is an established
Quranic fact. And if we are believers in the Quran, we have to be open to this. Not only open to
this, we have to know that there will be a messenger who will come and confirm all the prophets.
and we will have no aversion at all to this idea. In fact, we'll expect it and we'll agree with it
readily. We happen to be the lucky generation or the fortunate generation that witnesses the
fulfillment of this verse and I'm talking as, as one of you. You know, I distinguish in the Quran
between Muhammad, the messenger, and Muhammad, the man. And I'm telling you Rashad, the man, is very excited
about all the information that comes, so Rashad, the messenger. I'm just... I'm just... Along with you I cry and
I'm excited and they see me jump up and down in the mosque when the information comes and we all
jump together. Because it is just beautiful. God is teaching us and we are very fortunate to be born
now, at this time. Yeah, it sounds right. What does it say, Mohtasham?
Yes.
Exactly. Yeah, this is it.
Exactly. So, as you see the Quran goes out of its way to mention this
in the present tense because it is a continuous process until the
end of the world. Every village, every community is going to have messengers.
Look at Leila Intefaq. See. She is a messenger of God. When she goes to her college and she talks to
the people about God or worshipping God alone, she is a messenger of God and nobody can dispute that.
So, I hope this clarified the... and this is why you see the opposition vicious as they are,
they never never said Muhamma. is the last messenger. They cannot say that. They
know it's a fabricated lie. This is why they didn't come up with it. That's right. All they're trying
to do is that his name is not Rashad.
Ismail: They are trying to discredit you.
But they cannot come up with
any fact or any proof. They can only call me names which is exactly what the Quran says
and it is really miraculous. It is really miraculous. They called me the names that the
Quran says, specifically. It's like, you know, God is showing us that He knows what they're going to say.
Where I get this telegram from Ahmad Deedat addressed to Rashad Khalifa, AL-KAZZAB. OK. This is in
English, but he writes the Arabic word that is in the Quran. OK. And then we read in SURA, in SURA 38
and in SURA 54 the same word. They say how come in all of us, he's the one who's getting the message
and inspiration. He is KAZZAB. And then God goes on in Quran and says they will find out tomorrow who
is the KAZZAB. But they had to... I mean this is Western Union folks. OK. And they wrote down
K A Z Z A B. OK. It's not an English word. But it's exactly what God wrote in the Quran in SURA 38 and in SURA 54.
Ismail: Except that God spelled it correctly.
Exactly. It's KATHAB (کذاب) not KAZZAB (کزاب). They cannot do that.
But it's ironic. So, as you know, the minute the person calls you names, they lost the argument. They have
no evidence. When they start calling you stupid and this kind of thing. Then, you know they lost the argument.
Ismail: OK. We have time for a couple more questions.
Brother Azhar has...
Azhar: I just want you to come back on... there are a lot of verses that say the messenger has been destined to prevail, so that Islam will prevail over all religions. Can you just come back on that?
This is a prophecy in SURA number 9 and SURA number
48, that Islam will prevail over all religions and will go to all corners of the world.
And I believe... not I believe that... I know that. You know, this will happen. And IN SHA ALLAH, it will happen in our
generation. Brother Edip, yesterday, said that SURA 110 that talks about
(110:1) إِذَا جَآءَ نَصْرُ ٱللَّهِ وَٱلْفَتْحُ
When God's victory comes
and you see the people embracing God's religion in great numbers
(110:3) فَسَبِّحْ بِحَمْدِ رَبِّكَ وَٱسْتَغْفِرْهُ ۚ
Glorify your Lord and seek His forgiveness.
(110:3) إِنَّهُۥ كَانَ تَوَّابًۢا
These are 19 words. The generation before us know nothing about 19. We
are the generation of 19 and we are the generation that will witness this great victory IN SHA ALLAH.
And this is why this is the new world that did not receive a message before.
All the messengers came in the Middle East. So, the message had to come here to America. And
it is going to Japan. You just look at Naoko there. See, Naoko. Why did God send person from...?
Are you from Tokyo, Naoko? Are you from Tokyo or where else? From Tokyo. From the heart of Japan. So, you know
that the message will go there. And now when Naoko goes back, there's going to be true Japanese believers.
I think that's the last frontier and it will be in fulfillment of this prophecy of SURA 9 or SURA 48.
Ismail: Don't forget Mexico and Latin America.
We have the whole world covered. I think we'll have a break before lunch.